<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://leozhang88.github.io/</id>
    <title>Asia Trends</title>
    <updated>2019-10-10T10:02:42.035Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://leozhang88.github.io/"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://leozhang88.github.io//atom.xml"/>
    <logo>https://leozhang88.github.io//images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://leozhang88.github.io//favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2019, Asia Trends</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Korean Fashion – How to Dress up Korean Style]]></title>
        <id>https://leozhang88.github.io//post/korean-fashion-how-to-dress-up-korean-style</id>
        <link href="https://leozhang88.github.io//post/korean-fashion-how-to-dress-up-korean-style">
        </link>
        <updated>2019-10-10T09:20:08.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever thought of Korean fashion or dressing like a Korean celebrity you saw on TV? Or you admire Korean style but you do not know where to start? Well, below are some useful tips on how to dress like a Korean.</p>
<h2 id="korean-fashion-how-to-dress-up-korean-style">Korean Fashion – How to dress up Korean Style</h2>
<p>It is essential to note that the basic things needed in Korean fashion are similar to any other culture around the world. Even though it is a bit unique, some of the things are the same. One basic thing about Korean fashion to consider is the layering of clothes, and how you should mix different colors. For instance, black pants, red top, red shoes and a black bag might be too boring. So look for something creative. Below are some tips to help you put a perfect Korean look.</p>
<h3 id="choose-the-right-bottom-wear">Choose the right bottom-wear</h3>
<p>First, look for potential pants you can use. You can pick casual shorts, skirt, pants, leggings or a pair of jeans. Jeans are recommended because they can be matched with many things. But look for something you will be comfortable wearing. According to fashion experts, never sacrifice comfort for fashion. It may not work and even lead to disaster.</p>
<h3 id="choose-a-good-top">Choose a good top</h3>
<p>Choosing the right top will depend on the bottom-wear you choose. For example, if you choose tight pants, pick a loose and a long top, and if your bottom wear is not tight, choose a tight and a short top. If you want to wear plain-pants, a top that has designs and prints will look great. According to Korean fashion, dark-colored pants should be paired with light-colored tops.</p>
<h3 id="choose-the-right-shoes">Choose the right shoes</h3>
<p>The next important tip is putting on the right shoes. For instance, if you want to put on short-shorts, tight jeans, skirt or leggings, you have numerous options. You can put on high-cut sneakers, slippers, boots, sandals or doll shoes. If you are wearing pants with loose-end, then you are advised not to have high-cuts. Try to limit the length of the footwear up-to-the ankles. The shoes you choose will always say something about the fashion.</p>
<h3 id="accessorize">Accessorize</h3>
<p>The last thing you should not ignore is about accessories. Accessories will put more attention on the entire outfit. Korean fashion is well achieved by spicing your dressing. You can wear bangles, a long necklace, glasses, blazer, a scarf, a big bag and many more. However, do not wear many accessories all at once. You do not want to look like a crown or a Christmas tree with so many decorations.</p>
<p>Now you know the basics about Korean fashion. It is now easier to dress like a Korean with those simple outfits in your wardrobe. But it is always important to note that the secret of having a successful fashion lies on the person and not the outfit. Hence, be confident, simple and do not overdo it. With that in mind, step out and let everyone know you can pull off a perfect Korean style.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Japanese Fashion Trends Taking Over the Streets of Tokyo]]></title>
        <id>https://leozhang88.github.io//post/11 Japanese Fashion Trends Taking Over the Streets of Tokyo</id>
        <link href="https://leozhang88.github.io//post/11 Japanese Fashion Trends Taking Over the Streets of Tokyo">
        </link>
        <updated>2019-10-09T07:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When we think about Japanese fashion trends, our imagination often turns to over-the-top street stylings seen in the Harajuku district of Tokyo or in the pages of Fruits. While the distinct fashion subcultures showcased there are certainly still thriving, the streets of Tokyo are brimming with more accessible Japanese fashion trends bound to inspire your more adventurous outfit stylings.</p>
]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When we think about Japanese fashion trends, our imagination often turns to over-the-top street stylings seen in the Harajuku district of Tokyo or in the pages of Fruits. While the distinct fashion subcultures showcased there are certainly still thriving, the streets of Tokyo are brimming with more accessible Japanese fashion trends bound to inspire your more adventurous outfit stylings.</p>
<!-- more -->
<p>Japanese fashion girls put their own twist on jumpsuits in khaki and denim iterations, liven up ensembles with bold pops of bright yellow, play with proportions in dramatic maxi skirts and wide-leg pants, and ground their venturesome stylings with black leather shoes that range from classic (ankle boots or Mary Janes) to fashion-forward (platform brogues and pointed-toe flats that harken back to the Elizabethan era). Look no further than below for the latest in Japanese fashion trends.</p>
<p><img src="https://leozhang88.github.io//post-images/1570605319669.jpg" alt=""><br>
This bold outfit features two of Tokyo's big trends—oversize bottoms with wide-leg striped pants and pops of primary colors, and yellow graphic T-shirts balanced out by a bold red lip and matching heels.<br>
<img src="https://leozhang88.github.io//post-images/1570605376899.jpg" alt=""><br>
When the outfit takes a more subdued approach to color, interest is created by playing with proportions and incorporating unexpected textures. This oversize and intentionally ill-fitted suede coat does both of those things, and it finds footing with statement black leather shoes.<br>
<img src="https://leozhang88.github.io//post-images/1570605471247.jpg" alt=""><br>
It would be an understatement to reduce this floor-length canary yellow duster to a &quot;pop of primary color.&quot; Paired with the unexpected textures of a fur under layer, a bamboo handbag, and bold statement jewelry, the only subtle part of the outfit is the black leather boots.<br>
<img src="https://leozhang88.github.io//post-images/1570605493804.jpg" alt=""><br>
This denim jumpsuit look requires few additional accessories to make a statement. If you look closely, you'll see that it's actually a pair of wide-leg overalls topped off with a matching jean jacket. Black leather platform brogues give the denim-on-denim look an added cool factor, and the army-green bomber jacket brings it all together in colder weather.<br>
<img src="https://leozhang88.github.io//post-images/1570605512253.jpg" alt=""><br>
A true jumpsuit, the head-to-toe khaki look is livened up by a pop of primary color via the patterned silk scarf worn as a neckerchief. The jumpsuit's large fit is made chic with a black belt tied tightly at the waist and oversize bottoms tucked into black satin ankle boots.<br>
<img src="https://leozhang88.github.io//post-images/1570605530754.jpg" alt=""><br>
A tweed jacket and Mary Janes worn with socks make this ensemble wonderfully retro, but the bright pop of yellow and round sunglasses keep the look forward-thinking and cool.<br>
<img src="https://leozhang88.github.io//post-images/1570605551535.jpg" alt=""><br>
Unexpected textures combine with sneakers and athletic socks to create an eclectic ensemble. The look plays with proportions by incorporating a long paisley patterned coat with a knee-length button-down and a maxi skirt.<br>
<img src="https://leozhang88.github.io//post-images/1570605569708.jpg" alt=""><br>
This ensemble exhibits the oversize bottoms trend and plays with proportions. Wide-leg pants (worn extra long) and a blazer are unexpectedly cinched in at the waist with a matching black corset and topped off with an oversize trench coat.<br>
<img src="https://leozhang88.github.io//post-images/1570605592722.jpg" alt=""><br>
The jacquard effect of this maxi skirt adds a feminine touch to the otherwise all-black ensemble, while a leather biker jacket and black leather platform brogues add an edgy vibe.<br>
<img src="https://leozhang88.github.io//post-images/1570605612336.jpg" alt=""><br>
Elizabethan-esque black leather pointed-toe shoes get even funkier when they're worn with white socks and paired with lace-up pants and a cropped denim jacket with statement detailing.<br>
<img src="https://leozhang88.github.io//post-images/1570605630691.jpg" alt=""><br>
This maxi skirt and button-down pairing is made inimitably chic with an off-the-shoulder jacket, and black leather ankle boots pare down the entire ensemble.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>